Alhamdu Lillah.
We praise God.
Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
And we bear witness that there is no other god but the one God.
Last Friday, Abdullah presented to you evidence that the Friday prayer is mathematically coded. That it is required by God
to drop all business and come to the Friday prayer. He also presented evidence that the 2 sermons of the Friday prayer
are part of the prayer. They're counted as... in addition to the two units.
They complete the 4 units. So, I'm going to ask you to face this way. If you're not facing this way, to face this way. So, can you turn this way?
Cause...as if you are in the prayer. You can stay on the chair. Ihsan, you can stay on the chair. As long as you are facing this direction, it's OK.
I have fantastic news for you, but I will keep it for the second KHUTBAH to ensure that everyone who is supposed to be here
will be here. Meanwhile, I will... I want to thank many of you... most of you... all of you for wishing me a happy birthday last Friday.
And I want to use this to reflect on God's omnipotence. And the predetermination of the world
so that we have the freedom of choice at the same time.
A submitter, by definition, submits to God and believes whatever God says. The opposite, the non-submitter will follow what the parents
taught him or her. And this is repeated in the Quran in verse... SURA 2, verse 170. SURA 31, verse 21, and SURA 43, verses 22 and 23.
When they are told, the disbelievers, the non-submitters... when they are told follow what God says
They say no, we follow what our parents told us. So, this is the difference between a submitter and non-submitter.
Because when you are born, you are a new generation. And in your lifetime, God will reveal new information and new knowledge.
Knowledge is increasing in this world. And you are required to look at all this new knowledge and sift through it and accept or reject
whatever is... whatever God wants us to accept or reject. But God tells us in the Old Testament and the New Testament
and the Final Testament, the Quran, that He will send the Messenger of the Covenant. So, I'm going to read some of these with you.
In the last book of the Old Testament. Here's the New Testament. In the last book of the Old Testament, Malachi, chapter 3
under the subtitle, the Messenger of the Covenant: Lo, I am sending My messenger to prepare the way before Me.
And suddenly there will come to the temple, the Lord whom you seek and the Messenger of the Covenant whom you desire.
In the New Testament, in Luke 17:22. I'm gonna read it for you. Jesus is prophesying the coming of the Messenger of the Covenant.
Jesus said to the disciples a time will come when you will long to see one day of the son of man, but you will not see it.
They will tell you he is to be found in this place or that. Do not go running about it excitedly. The son of man in his day
will be like the lightning that flashes from one end of the day to the other. First, however, he must suffer much
and be rejected by the present age. As it was in the days of Noah, so it will be in the days of the son of man.
They ate and drank. They took husbands and wives right up to the day Noah entered the Ark. And when the flood came
it destroyed them all. It was much the same in the days of Lot. They ate and drank. They bought and sold. They built and planted.
But on the day, Lot left Sodom, fire and brimstone rained down from heaven and destroyed them all.
It will be like that on the day of the son of man... It will be like that on the day the son of man is revealed.
On that day, if a man is on the rooftop and his belongings are in the house, he should not go down to get them.
Neither should the man in the field return home. Remember Lot's wife. Whoever tries to preserve his life will lose it.
Whoever loses it keeps it. And this is relevant to the second sermon... second KHUTBAH.
I tell you on that night, there will be two men in one bed. One will be taken and the other left.
Two women will be grinding grain together. One will be taken and the other left. Also in Mathew 24:27.
24:27. As the lightning from the east flashes to the west, so will the coming of the son of man be.
So, it's gonna be every person on Earth is going to hear about God's plan and the Messenger of the Covenant.
In the Final Testament, you're all familiar with the verse... verse 81 in SURA 3
where God says that after all the prophets have delivered their messages, God will send the Messenger of the Covenant
to consolidate the messages, purify them, and deliver the one message, the one unified message
and preach the one unified religion acceptable by God. This is in the Quran 3:81.
From these looking at the Old Testament, the New Testament and the Final Testament and seeing that God is telling us
that He will send the Messenger of the Covenant. And for us to be fortunate to be born at this time.
I mean, when will he come, the Messenger of the Covenant? It's gonna be some day, like a Tuesday of a week
a certain day of a month. We just happen to exist at the time when God is executing this plan.
And as submitters, we are required to believe God. And I want to say that the difference between believing God, in this respect
and disbelieving is the difference between the highest Heaven and the lowest pit of Hell.
Therefore, it is my responsibility to help you and help myself strengthen our faith
strengthen our belief in this regard so long as we have the absolute proof, the physical evidence.
And this is what I wanted to share with you.
Edip, where are the markers?
I talked to my mother this morning and I told her and I told her... I asked her what time was I born?
And she said don't ask questions like that.
I said OK, Mom. Did the midwife come during the day or during the night?
She said they came in the middle of the night. Anyway, she's still giving me instructions, you know.
Doesn’t matter how old you are, you're still a baby.
November 19. That was the Birthday and I was thanking you for celebrating it with me.
And this is a calendar that gives the number of every day of the year. It just happens that November 19 is the only day of the
year whose number is a multiple of 19, also.
Now, January 19 is the 19th day of the year. So, you don't count that. It's just like saying 1 is divisible by 1.
You know 1 is 1 and is not divisible. So, February 19 is the 50th day. It's not divisible by 19.
March 19 is the 78th day. It's not a multiple of 19. The 19th of April is the 109th day. It's number 109.
It's not a multiple of 19. The 19th of May is 1 3 9. Number 139, not a multiple of 19. The 19th of June is number 170
missed by 1. The 19th of July is number 200. The 19th of August is number 2 3 1. The 19th of September
is number 262. It's not a multiple of 19. The 19th of October is 292. It's not a multiple of 19.
November 19th is number 323. It's a multiple of 19. 19th of December is number 353. It's not a multiple of 19.
So, November 19 is the only day of the year whose number is a multiple of 19. What does this tell us?
And my mother was sterile for 4 years before I was born, by the way. So, this means God designed, you know
This tells us about God's power that He knew in advance that this baby is gonna grow up and is assigned to him
finding the code 19 in the Quran which is very simple, existed in the Quran for 1400 years. And
I want to quote Batool Karmally's very simple rebuttal of people who say who don't believe
She says so just explain why did he find the number 19, the code 19? So, God knew in advance who He was assigning this to
and He picked out the only day in the year that is dated 19 and its number is a multiple of 19.
There's something else I wanted to say. What is it? Yes. Now, this means 266 days before this date, there has to be a conception.
I mean, God planned the pregnancy and the birth and this is before we come to this world.
and this is... this is a time also to share with you a discovery by Azhar Khan.
These are the Arabic alphabet and the gematrical value of the Arabic alphabet.
As you know, we tell the people that 19 means One. The gematrical value of the word... of the number 19 or the word One is 19.
And 19 is God's signature. We're gonna find 19 is God's signature in all His creation, the Sun, the moon, you.
You have 209 bones in your body. 19 times 11. Dr. Sabahi gave us a lecture on the elements in the universe.
And the maximum number of electrons is 114. A multiple of 19.
So, Azhar Khan put the gematrical values... Oh, when we tell the people, the skeptics
that 19 is the numerical value of the word One, that God is proclaiming there's only one God. You shall worship God alone.
The first commandment in the Old Testament, the New Testament and the Final Testament, they tell you how do we know that
19 is the value of One? OK. Azhar Khan put the values of these, the gematrical values of all the letters
up to 1000 which is the letter... the last letter غ and he found that this number is a multiple of 19. So, this validates
the value of every alphabet letter in the Arabic language. And this tells us that God designed
the Arabic language and designed the Quran with the code 19 in it before the Earth was created.
Therefore, it is not too much to also the student who is to research this code 19 is born on the 19th day
of a month, the only day in the year, that is also divisible by 19. The purpose of sharing this with you
against my own personal tendency is because I want to strengthen your faith and my faith.
This is one of the things that God associates with the number 19 in SURA 74.
(74:31) وَيَزْدَادَ ٱلَّذِينَ ءَامَنُوٓا۟ إِيمَـٰنًۭا
the believers, they increase in faith.
There's another thing. We were using this same alphabet yesterday. My sister compiled my name. She numbered them consecutively
regardless of the gematrical value. And she calculated my name and it came out to 114, the total of the letters.
So, all this tells us that God predetermined and predesigned all these things and all you can say SUBHAN ALLAH, glory be to God
that He is Omnipotent. And I better stop at this point to leave some room for the great news coming up.
Tooboo Ela Allah. Repent.
Alhamdu Lillah.
We praise God.
Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
And we bear witness that there is no other god except the one God.
The great news that I have for you started out with a few questions by Lisa and the discussion that followed. And then,
as I will share with you the verses in the Quran we have been reading them hundreds of times, but you will see how
how logical and beautiful they fold together. The great news is that the righteous go straight to Heaven.
This is the great news. Then, I'm gonna give you the evidence. In other words, they do not... the unrighteous go to death. They die.
The unrighteous do not really die. They certainly move from one stage to next stage in a gentle way.
There's a SURA that says... that says that the angels of death snatch the souls of the disbelievers
and they beat them up by the time of death. In verses... in SURA 8 verse 51. In SURA 47, verse 27
God is telling us that the angels who are guarding us now and serving us,
when the time comes and the person who dies a disbeliever, they beat the person, specifically on the face and the rear end.
You can imagine. Also, they snatch the soul because obviously this disbeliever is going to Hell.
But before that there is a period of death and a continuous nightmare. This is what the Quran teaches us.
In SURA 40, God says they see Hell everyday, but they do not enter it until the day of... the Day of Resurrection... the Day of Judgement.
because Hell is not here yet. Now, look at God's wisdom and mercy.
God's wisdom and mercy is that He created Heaven, first, before we were brought here and He put Adam and Eve there.
The Earth was here. Yes, it is egg-shaped. And Adam and Eve were up here in Heaven connected with their bodies down here.
This is some kind of invisible connection. But the souls of Adam and Eve - this is all allegorical - were up there in Heaven enjoying Heaven.
Therefore, Heaven exists. When they broke God's law, they were brought down here. They were sucked back into their bodies.
But Heaven exists and this is where we go the moment of death. It is exactly like when we sleep. When you and I sleep, the righteous
their soul voluntarily roams around. And this is exactly how the righteous die.
They just leave their bodies here on Earth. And through the bodies disintegrate and go away, but that doesn’t matter
because we're gonna be coupled again with new bodies on the Day of Resurrection. But the righteous go straight to Heaven.
Now, here's the startling evidence. In the same SURA, where God tells us that the angels of death snatch
death is a painful process for the unrighteous. And the angels snatch their souls out of their bodies. They're resisting.
And they're being beaten up cause this is the day they receive the bad news. At the time of death, every person knows whether
he or she is going to Heaven or Hell through these very clear verses. In the same SURA, God says that the angels invite the righteous.
It's an invitation. And it's met by joy. It's like the angel come at you and say now, you can go to Heaven. You say really! Is it time?
So, in the... so, we're told that eagerly the righteous move on to the next stage. And it is beautiful.
As the descriptions in SURA 2 verse 25. Now notice
these things that we read hundreds of times but this is the time that God wants to inform us, tell us this good news.
God says give good news to those who believe and lead a righteous life that they have deserved gardens with flowing streams.
When provided with a provision of fruits therein, they say this is what was provided for us previously. The key word here is provision.
OK. Now, God says... this is a commandment... in SURA 3 verse 169... well, let me go in the same SURA 2, first.
SURA 2 verse 154, God says do not say about those who are killed in the cause of God that they are dead.
Do not say that they are dead. Because for they are alive at their Lord. In this verse says they are alive but you do not perceive.
Now, this is one. In SURA 3 verse 169, God says do not think that those who are killed in the cause of God are dead
for they are alive at their Lord being provided. The same word is used as in 2:25, provision.
And then we are told in a number of verses that it is not just... you don't have to fight in the cause of God and get a gun or something
and get killed. That... when the righteous die, also, that death as a righteous or... or... or being killed in the cause of God, either way
is the same. And we see this in SURA 22, verse 58, for example, 22:58.
That's a good one.
That's 4:69. 4:69
Now, looking at 22:58, says those who emigrated for the sake of God, then got killed or died, either way
God will surely shower them with good provisions. The same words are being used.
(22:58) لَيَرْزُقَنَّهُمُ ٱللَّهُ رِزْقًا حَسَنًۭا
The same repetition of the same words in the same verse. So, God says: do not say about those who
who died or get killed in the cause of God as dead. We cannot say that. They do not die. The righteous do not die. They simply move on
from this world to another stage on a very joyous and very happy day. Here's another clue that is really strong.
And this is in 44:56.
Now, we read about the two deaths and two lives, right? These are the disbelievers. In SURA 40 verse 12
The disbeliever says our Lord, You put us to death twice and You gave us two lives. Is there any way out of Hell?
The disbeliever say that. In the beginning of SURA 2, God says how can you disbelieve in God when He...
when He... when you were dead and He gave you life. Then, He puts you to death. Then, He gives you life.
But this is talking to the disbelievers. Now, watch what the believers say. SURA 56... 44:56
They never taste death therein beyond the first death. He has spared them the retribution of Hell. Now, this is... this is a very powerful clue.
In Arabic
(44:56) لَا يَذُوقُونَ فِيهَا ٱلْمَوْتَ إِلَّا ٱلْمَوْتَةَ ٱلْأُولَىٰ
Except the first death.
So, the second death for the righteous is not death at all. It's just like going to sleep and it is...and the angels come and invite you
to go on to a fantastic place. And it is... it is met with joy and happiness. Is this great news or is this great news?
Alhamdu Lillah.
Let's see what else did I forget, here.
Oh, this is very important. I've nearly forgot it because now I'm gonna impress it on you. Cause you will never forget it.
This makes it special. And it is very important. In SURA 36, verse 20. And you can read it again. 36 starting from 20 to 27.
This gives the whole story away. I mean really proves it. 36:20
SURA YA SEEN.
OK. It says a man coming...came running... a man came running from the other side of the city saying O, my people
follow the messengers. Follow those who do not ask you for any wage and are guided.
Why should I not worship the One who initiated me and to Him is your ultimate return?
Shall I set up besides Him powerless gods? If the Most Gracious willed any harm for me, the intercession will not help me one bit.
Nor can they rescue me. Then, I will be totally astray.
I have believed in your Lord. Please, listen to me. Now, this is a man who's asking his people to worship God alone.
Number 26. (At the time of his death,) this is in parentheses, my... my own words. This shall be in the final translation, IN SHAA ALLAH.
do not... I'm not using this word death. he was told... Listen to this. enter Paradise or enter Heaven. he said O, I wish my people knew.
that my Lord has forgiven me and made me honorable. Now, why would he say I wish my people knew? Because obviously
his people are there on Earth. He's up here in Heaven.
His people are down here, but they do not know. Remember the verse? But you do not perceive.
So, he's up here in Heaven and he says I wish my people know.
But it is God's... it is the test and it is God's wisdom that Khomeini cannot come back and tell us where he is now. People
People, once they cross that line, they cannot come back here and tell us. But God is telling us. And this man obviously went to Heaven
and he's saying I wish my people knew that my Lord has forgiven me and made me honorable.
So, is that in Old Testament or New Testament?
This is the Final Testament.
Aqem Al-Salat.
Allahu Akbar. Allahu Akbar. La Elaha Ella Allah.